Maryanne Exempliarova

UX/UI Designer

1	Argentina, Buenos Aires
\bigvee	exemaryanne@gmail.com
	maryanne-exe.github.io
in	linkedin.com/in/maryannexe

Summary -

I'm a 23 years old UX/UI designer from Russia and live in Buenos Aires. I have a Bachelor's degree in Computer Science and during my studies I was gaining experience in programming, design and 3d graphics. Afterwards I found myself in User Experience Design.

Have an experience creating UIs for web-based applications, mobile and desktop. Worked with Apple HIG, Material Design and Windows guidelines. Familiar with web front-end development (HTML, CSS, some JavaScript) and iOS UI development in Xcode.

Work History _____

Lead UX/UI Designer

JSC Radiomonitoring Technologies

Jan 2015 - Aug 2015 St. Petersburg, Russia

Worked on several top secret software products for military radio monitoring for desktop (Windows, Linux) and mobile platforms (Windows phone and Android). My role:

- Redesign legacy UIs;
- Embed UX stage in products' development workflow;
- Detect and analyze usability problems of current interfaces and find the ways of tackling them;
- Develop low-fidelity mockups and pixel-perfect designs;
- Work with guidelines: Material, Windows Modern Design, also create custom consistent and clear UIs;
- Prepare designs for UI developers;
- Track the progress of UI developers' work checking for design compliance.

UX/UI Designer JetBrains

Aug 2014 - Nov 2014 St. Petersburg, Russia

Worked on web-based project called TeamCity. My role:

- Identify and analyze issues in current interface;
- Uniform UI regarding guidelines of other company's products;
- Create low-fidelity and pixel-perfect mockups;
- Prepare designs for UI developers and monitor process of it's realization regarding design concepts.

UX/UI Designer NKS Jan 2014 - Aug 2014 St. Petersburg, Russia

Here I was taking part in developing web-based news service and iOS application for delivering food using Xamarin Studio. My role was to improve usability of news service and design iOS application from scratch.

3D Artist wargaming.net

Aug 2013 - Jan 2014 St. Petersburg, Russia

My role was to develop realistic historical based 3d models of World War II naval ships and draw freehand textures for them for World of Warships video game.

Junior .NET Developer
Lifeactive

Sep 2011 - Aug 2013 St. Petersburg, Russia

Take part in development web-based applications/part-time work.

Education

Bachelor's degree

2009 - 2013

Saint Petersburg State Polytechnical University

Applied Computer Science in Design